Nemi Sanghvi

Web Designer

Energetic Web Designer with **2.5 + years** of experience creating and maintaining functional, attractive and responsive websites for **Crypto Currency**, **Learning Platforms and Consultant Websites**. Clear understanding of modern technologies and best design practices. Experienced with **Wordpress** and **ReactJS Designing**. Proven track records of website scores and **customer retention**.

Work History

2022-02 -Current

Web Designer at MultiQoS

MultiQoS - Web & Mobile App Development Company, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- Designing personalized websites for fresher, middle and senior level clients.
- Proficient in HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JQuery,
 Responsive Mobile Design, ReactJS Designing,
 WordPress and Media Query.
- Editing & Design with designing team in the company to build perfect web designs.
- Modifying and making changes according to client's requirements.
- Checking for errors and de-bugging websites.
- Maintaining Excel sheet and regularly updating data.
- Good knowledge of Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD and Zeplin.
- Good Knowledge of Git and Version control system.

2020-10 -2022-01

Web Designer at Rayo Innovations

Web Designer, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- I had worked there on the conversion of PSD to HTML5 using Bootstrap skills
- Creating website layouts and user interfaces using standard HTML5 and CSS3 practices.
- Understands the **client requirement** easily
- Worked closely with **team leader** to maintain

Contact

Address

C/302 Dharnidhar Tower Opp, Dharnidhar Derasar Vasna Ahmedabad, GJ, 380001

Phone

726-598-5208

E-mail

nemisanghvi5@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nemi-sanghvib0495717a

WWW

https://nemisanghvi.github.io/portfolio/

Skills

HTML5, CSS3, Jquery



Wordpress



Adobe Photoshop, Adobe XD, Zeplin



Bootstrap



optimum levels of communication to effectively and efficiently complete projects.

- Communicating and assisting various departments throughout the design and production process.
- Implementing, testing, and maintaining the websites
 Design kept in mind.

2019-10 -2020-04

Internship at MoveoApps

Html Developer, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

- I had worked with the company in the conversion of PSD to HTML.
- I got an good opportunity to work with a company environment and dealing with other employee's.
- Learnt a lot of things there for a Web Designer position with implementation. E.g. Adobe Photoshop and Static website.

Education

2016-06 -

Bachelor of Science: Computer Engineering

2020-05

Gandhinagar Institute of Technology

CGPA: **7.94** SPI: **10.00**

2015-06 -

Associate of Science: H.S.E.

2016-03

Gujarat Law Society (GLS)

Percentage: 65%

2013-06 -

Associate of Science: S.S.E

2014-03

Gujarat Law Society (GLS)

Percentile: 75.30

Web Designer



Mobile Responsive Design



Time Management



Very Good

Deadline-driven



Team player



Languages

English



Hindi



Gujarati

